const STORE = [
  {question:'What year was the first Women\'s World Cup held?', 
  answers: ['1961','1971','1981','1991'],
  correct: '1991'
  },

  {question:'What US field player played goalie during a world cup match when the starting goalie got a red card?', 
  answers: ['Michelle Akers', 'Mia Hamm','Alex Morgan','Abby Wambach'], correct:'Mia Hamm'},

  {question:'What Brazilian superstar has gained the nickname "Pele in skirts", which Pele himself has endorsed?', 
  answers:['Marta', 'Maria', 'Maya', 'Madonna'], 
  correct:'Marta'},

  {question:'What professional club is touted as the best-supported women\'s team in the world?',
  answers:['Olympique Lyon','Orlando Pride', 'Arsenal Women\'s FC','Portland Thorns FC'],
  correct:'Portland Thorns FC'},

  {question:'What is the nickname of the Australian Women\'s National Team?',answers:['The Sheilas','The Kangakickers','The Matildas','The Footys'], correct:'The Matildas'},

  {question:'What US player is known for taking off her shirt in celebration following her \'99 World Cup winning penalty kick?', 
  answers: ['Brandi Chastain','Mia Hamm','Tiffany Milbrett','Julie Foudy'], correct:'Brandi Chastain'},

  {question:'Which collegiate dynasty boasts winning 16 of the first 20 Women\'s Soccer National Championships?', 
  answers:['Stanford','UCLA','UNC Chapel Hill','University of Portland'], correct:'UNC Chapel Hill'},

  {question:'Who is the first American player to leave college early and directly enter the National Women\'s Soccer League?', 
  answers: ['Allie Long','Mallory Pugh','Mia Hamm','Alex Morgan'], correct:'Mallory Pugh'},

  {question:'What former US Women\'s National member has declared her intention to run for US Soccer President?', 
  answers: ['Hope Solo','Briana Scurry','Christie Rampone','Megan Rapinoe'], correct:'Hope Solo'},

  {question:'Which player has NOT been featured on a cover of the popular video game series FIFA?', 
  answers: ['Steph Catley','Christine Sinclair','Alex Morgan ','Amadine Henry'], 
  correct:'Amadine Henry'},
];